Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRE-GOVERNMENT CAREER FILE, 1945-1971 (Boxes 74-111)
  - Correspondence
    - Derounian, Steven B. (Box-folder 80: 6)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box-folder 80: 7)
    - Dickler, Gerald (Box-folder 80: 8)
    - Dulles, Allen (Box-folder 80: 9)
    - E (Box-folder 80: 10)
    - Ettinger, Karl E. (Box-folder 80: 11)
    - F (Box-folder 80: 12)
    - Ferrara, Joseph A. (Box-folder 80: 13)
    - Finch, Robert H. (Box-folder 80: 14)
    - FitzMorris, Paul E. (Box-folder 80: 15)
    - Fragos, Chris (Box-folder 80: 16)
    - G (Box-folder 80: 17)
    - Gamble, Edward W., Jr. (Box-folder 80: 18)
    - Ginsberg, Norman (Box-folder 80: 19)
    - Giovannelli, Ronald (Box-folder 80: 20)
    - Grandval, Gilbert (Box-folder 80: 21)
    - Guillermin, Henri (Box-folder 80: 22)
    - H (Box-folder 80: 23)
    - Hagan, John G. (Box-folder 80: 24)
    - Hall, Leonard W. (Box-folder 80: 25)
    - Horton, Philip (Box-folder 80: 26)
    - Hrubý, Blahoslav S. (Box-folder 80: 27)
    - I-J (Box-folder 81: 1)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box-folder 81: 2)
    - Jolis, Albert E. (Box-folder 81: 3)
    - K (Box-folder 81: 4)
    - Katz, Milton (Box-folder 81: 5)
    - Keating, Kenneth B. (Box-folder 81: 6)
    - Kivlan, John (Box-folder 81: 7)
    - L (Box-folder 81: 8)
    - Langan, Thomas G. (Box-folder 81: 9)
    - Lawlor, Reed C. (Box-folder 81: 10)
    - Lizza, Al (Box-folder 81: 11)
    - Lord, Walter (Box-folder 81: 12)
    - M (Box-folder 81: 13)
    - McCone, John A. (Box-folder 81: 14)
    - McGovern, Eugene (Box-folder 81: 15)
    - Marino, Ralph J. (Box-folder 81: 16)
    - Martin, David (Box-folder 81: 17)
    - Martin, Rose L. (Box-folder 81: 18)
    - Morgan, Thomas O. (Box-folder 81: 19)
    - N (Box-folder 81: 20)
    - Needham, James J. (Box-folder 81: 21)
    - Newkirk, Russell E. (Box-folder 81: 22)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 81: 23)
    - O (Box-folder 82: 1)
    - O'Keefe, Paul T. (Box-folder 82: 2)
    - P (Box-folder 82: 3)
    - Quinn, William W. (Box-folder 82: 4)
    - R (Box-folder 82: 5)
    - Regnery, Henry (Box-folder 82: 6)
    - Renander, Arthur W., Jr. (Box-folder 82: 7)
    - Rice, Raymond J. (Box-folder 82: 8)
    - Riordan, Michael (Box-folder 82: 9)
    - Ris, Joseph (Box-folder 82: 10)
    - Rooney, J. Patrick (Box-folder 82: 11)
    - Roosevelt, P. James (Box-folder 82: 12)
    - Rosselli, Jean-Pierre (Box-folder 82: 13)
    - S (Box-folder 82: 14)
    - Sackheim, Maxwell (Box-folder 82: 15)
    - Sebastian, Frank P. (Box-folder 82: 16)
    - Shaheen, John M. (Box-folder 82: 17)
    - Smith, David W. (Box-folder 82: 18)
    - Speno, Edward J. (Box-folder 82: 19)
    - Sullivan, Michael J. (Box-folder 82: 20)
    - T (Box-folder 82: 21)
    - Thomas, Lowell (Box-folder 82: 22)
    - Thornburg, James F. (Box-folder 82: 23)
  - Subject file A
    Primarily correspondence, memoranda, reports, and meeting materials.
    - American Bar Association (Box-folder 83: 1)
    - American Investors Fund (Box-folder 83: 2)
    - Americans for Winning the Peace (Box-folder 83: 3)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box-folder 83: 4)
    - Association for the Help of Retarded Children (Box-folder 83: 5)
    - Bar Association of Nassau County, New York (Box-folder 83: 6)
    - Betty Cashman Drama Studios (Box-folder 83: 7)
    - Boys' Clubs of America (Box-folder 83: 8)
    - Brookings Institution (Box-folder 83: 9)
    - C. W. Post College (Long Island University) (Box-folder 83: 10)
    - Catholic Charities (Diocese of Rockville Centre, New York)
      - General
        - Legal status (Box-folder 83: 11)
        - United Fund of Long Island relations (Box-folder 83: 12)
      - 1963-1964 (Box-folder 83: 13)
      - 1965
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 84: 1)
        - Contributor lists (Box-folder 84: 2)
        - Meeting materials and miscellany (Box-folder 84: 3)
      - 1966-1968 (Box-folder 84: 4)
      - 1969-1971 (Box-folder 84: 5)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box-folder 84: 6)
    - Chairmen's Club of Nassau County (New York) (Box-folder 84: 7)
    - Charles F. Noyes Company (Box-folder 84: 8)
    - Citizens Committee for Peace with Security (re Anti-Ballistic Missile System) (Box-folder 85: 1)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box-folder 85: 2)
    - Committee on Catholic Education (Archdiocese of New York) (Box-folder 85: 3)
    - Congressional Club (Fourth Congressional District, New York) (Box-folder 85: 4)
    - Elections
      - 1946 (Congressional campaigns) (Box-folder 85: 5)
      - 1948 (Thomas E. Dewey presidential campaign)
        - Correspondence and miscellany (Box-folder 85: 6)
        - Campaign literature and internal campaign memoranda (Box-folder 85: 7)
        - Post-mortems (Box-folder 85: 8)
      - 1952 (Dwight D. Eisenhower presidential campaign)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 85: 9)
        - Campaign literature and internal campaign memoranda (Box-folder 86: 1)
        - Post-election (Box-folder 86)
          - Correspondence and miscellany (Box-folder 86: 2)
          - Appointments to federal office (Box-folder 86: 3)
          - Republican National Committee internal documents (Box-folder 86: 4)
      - 1956 (potential Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign) (Box-folder 86: 5)
      - 1958 (Leonard W. Hall New York gubernatorial campaign)., Financial records (Box-folder 86: 6)
      - 1958 (Leonard W. Hall New York gubernatorial campaign)., Financial records (contd.) (Box-folder 87: 1)
      - 1960 (Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 87: 2)
        - Campaign literature and internal campaign memoranda (Box-folder 87: 3-4)
        - Background materials (Box-folder 88: 1)
        - Miscellany (Box-folder 88: 2)
      - 1964 (potential Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign) (Box-folder 88: 3)
      - 1968 (Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 88: 4)
        - Task Force on Tax Policy (advisory to Nixon during campaign) (Box-folder 88)
          - Reports (Box-folder 88: 5)
          - Background materials (Box-folder 88: 6)
          - Miscellany (Box-folder 88: 7)
        - Post-election correspondence (Box-folder 89: 1)
    - Filmsort microfilm products (Box-folder 89: 2)
    - Fordham University
      - Correspondence
        - 1956-1966 (Box-folder 89: 3)
        - 1967-1971 (Box-folder 89: 4)
      - Board of Trustees minutes and meeting materials
        - 1967 (Box-folder 89: 5)
        - 1968 (Box-folder 89: 6)
        - 1969 (Box-folder 89: 7)
        - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 90: 1)
      - Fundraising activities (Box-folder 90: 2)
      - Corporate Committee (Box-folder 90: 3)
      - President's Committee (Box-folder 90: 4)
      - Miscellany., Includes publicity re WJC (Box-folder 90: 5)
    - Friendly Sons of St. Patrick (Box-folder 90: 6)
    - Good Counsel College (Box-folder 90: 7)
    - Governor's Club (New York) (Box-folder 90: 8)
    - Hofstra University (Box-folder 90: 9)
    - Holle Verlag (Box-folder 91: 1)
    - Institute for Business Planning
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 91: 2)
      - Minutes (Box-folder 91: 3)
      - Microfilm information retrieval project (Box-folder 91: 4-5)
      - Microfilm information retrieval project (contd.) (Box-folder 92: 1)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 92: 2)
    - Institute for Strategic Studies (Great Britain) (Box-folder 92: 3)
    - International Rescue Committee
      - Correspondence
        - 1966-1968 (Box-folder 92: 4)
        - 1969-1971 (Box-folder 92: 5)
      - Executive Committee minutes
        - 1966-1969 (Box-folder 92: 6)
        - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 92: 7)
      - Financial statements (Box-folder 92: 8)
      - Fundraising activities (Box-folder 92: 9)
      - Annual reports (Box-folder 93: 1)
      - Publicity. Includes publicity re WJC (Box-folder 93: 2)
      - Donovan Emergency Commission to Investigate Communist Redefection Campaigns. Report, 1956 March 20 (Box-folder 93: 3-5)
      - Regional activity reports
        - Argentina (Box-folder 93: 6)
        - Botswana (Box-folder 93: 7)
        - Cambodia (Box-folder 93: 8)
        - Chile (Box-folder 93: 9)
        - Cuba (Box-folder 93: 10)
        - Haiti (Box-folder 93: 11)
        - Hong Kong (Box-folder 93: 12)
        - Laos (Box-folder 93: 13)
        - Middle East (Box-folder 93: 14)
        - North Africa (Box-folder 93: 15)
        - Peru (Box-folder 93: 16)
        - Taiwan (Box-folder 93: 17)
        - Vietnam (Box-folder 94)
          - 1965 (Box-folder 94: 1)
          - 1966 (Box-folder 94: 2)
          - Reports on Vietnam (by WJC), 1966 May (Box-folder 94: 3)
            Includes related correspondence and miscellany re WJC's trip to Vietnam.
          - 1967 (Box-folder 94: 4)
          - 1968-1970 (Box-folder 94: 5)
        - West Africa (mainly re Biafra) (Box-folder 94: 6)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 94: 7)
    - Johns Hopkins University Bologna Center (Box-folder 94: 8-9)
    - Kalb, Voorhis and Company (Box-folder 95: 1)
    - Knights and Ladies of the Equestrian Order of the Holy Sepulchre of Jerusalem (Box-folder 95: 2)
    - Knights of Malta (Box-folder 95: 3)
    - Koster-Dana Corporation (Box-folder 95: 4)
    - Law Research Service (Box-folder 95: 5)
    - League to Save Carthage (Box-folder 95: 6)
    - Legal Aid Society (Box-folder 95: 7)
    - Long Island Art Festival (Box-folder 95: 8)
    - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 95: 9)
      - Board of Directors minutes and meeting materials (Box-folder 95: 10)
      - Financial statements (Box-folder 95: 11)
      - Membership records (Box-folder 96: 1)
      - Policy declarations and position statements (Box-folder 96: 2)
      - Bureau of Government Research (Box-folder 96: 3)
      - Legislative Counsel (Box-folder 96: 4)
      - Public Affairs Council (Box-folder 96: 5)
      - Research Foundation (Box-folder 96: 6)
      - Trade Mission to Europe, 1970 (Box-folder 96: 7)
      - Issues file
        - Airports (Box-folder 96: 8)
        - Bridges (Box-folder 96: 9)
        - Conservation (Box-folder 96: 10)
        - Crime and delinquency (Box-folder 96: 11)
        - Economic development (Box-folder 97: 1)
        - Education (Box-folder 97: 2)
        - Housing (Box-folder 97: 3)
        - Legislation pending (Box-folder 97: 4)
        - Long Island Rail Road (Box-folder 97: 5)
        - Mitchel Field (air base) (Box-folder 97: 6)
        - New York State Constitution (Box-folder 97: 7)
        - Public finance (Box-folder 97: 8)
        - Strikes (Box-folder 97: 9)
        - Transportation (Box-folder 98: 1)
        - Welfare and poverty (Box-folder 98: 2)
      - Directory of Commerce and Industry for Nassau and Suffolk Counties (Box-folder 98: 3)
      - Long Island Facts Book (Box-folder 98: 4)
      - Miscellany., Includes publicity re WJC (Box-folder 98: 5)
    - Long Island Research Center (Box-folder 98: 6)
    - Long Island Theatre Society (Box-folder 98: 7)
    - Long Island University (Box-folder 98: 8)
    - Mercy Hospital (Long Island, New York) (Box-folder 98: 9)
    - Mill River Club (Upper Brookville, New York) (Box-folder 98: 10)
    - Million Dollar Round Table (Box-folder 98: 11)
    - Molloy Catholic College for Women (Box-folder 98: 12)
    - Nassau Citizens' Development Corporation (Box-folder 98: 13)
    - Nassau County [New York] Republican Committee (Box-folder 98: 14)
    - Nassau Lawyers' Association of Long Island (Box-folder 98: 15)
    - National Conference of Bar Examiners (Box-folder 98: 16)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box-folder 98: 17)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box-folder 99: 1)
    - New York Law Journal (Box-folder 99: 2)
    - New York State Bar Association (Box-folder 99: 3)
    - New York University (Box-folder 99: 4)
    - Penn Central Railroad (Box-folder 99: 5)
    - Practising Law Institute (Box-folder 99: 6)
    - Private Opinions, Inc. (polling company) (Box-folder 99: 7)
    - Public Affairs Research (organization) (Box-folder 99: 8)
    - Republican Party (Box-folder 99: 9)
    - Robert A. Taft Institute of Government (Box-folder 99: 10)
    - Rockford College (Box-folder 99: 11)
    - Romney, George (Box-folder 99: 12)
    - St. Francis Hospital (Roslyn, New York) (Box-folder 99: 13)
    - St. John's University (Box-folder 99: 14)
    - Saint Mary's College (Notre Dame, Indiana) (Box-folder 99: 15)
    - St. Mary's Dominican College (New Orleans, Louisiana) (Box-folder 100: 1)
    - San Juan (Puerto Rico) refuse disposal plant (Box-folder 100: 2)
    - Servo Corporation (Box-folder 100: 3)
    - Sky Island Club (Long Island, New York) (Box-folder 100: 4)
    - Trusts and Estates (Box-folder 100: 5)
    - Universal Reference System (Box-folder 100: 6)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S.
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - 1960-1967 (Box-folder 100: 7)
          - 1968-1971 (Box-folder 100: 8)
        - Donovan, William J. (Box-folder 100: 9)
        - Opera Mundi (Box-folder 100: 10)
        - Special Forces Club (London, England) (Box-folder 100: 11)
      - Visit of veterans of the French resistance movement to the United States as guests of Veterans of the O.S.S., 1959 (Box-folder 101: 1)
      - Visit of members of Veterans of the O.S.S. to France as guests of Action Amicale, 1960
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 101: 2-3)
        - Programs, press releases, biographical data (Box-folder 101: 4)
        - Miscellany (Box-folder 101: 5)
      - William J. Donovan Award (Box-folder 101: 6)
      - Newsletters (Box-folder 102: 1)
      - Miscellany. (Box-folder 102: 2)
        Includes publicity re WJC
  - Subject file B
    Primarily printed matter.
    - Accounting (Box-folder 102: 3)
    - Aerospace (Box-folder 102: 4)
    - Africa (Box-folder 102: 5)
    - Air and water pollution (Box-folder 102: 6)
    - Airports (Box-folder 102: 7)
    - Americans abroad (Box-folder 102: 8)
    - Apartment house projects (Box-folder 102: 9)
    - Asia (Box-folder 102: 10)
    - Automation (Box-folder 102: 11)
    - Bankruptcy (Box-folder 102: 12)
    - Bell and Howell Company Micro Photo Division (Box-folder 103: 1)
    - Bridges (Box-folder 103: 2)
    - Campaigning (Box-folder 103: 3)
    - Canada (Box-folder 103: 4)
    - Capitalism (Box-folder 103: 5)
    - Centers for international studies (Box-folder 103: 6)
    - Checks (Box-folder 103: 7)
    - China (Box-folder 103: 8)
    - Churchill, Winston (Box-folder 103: 9)
    - Cities and states (Box-folder 103: 10)
    - Civil rights (Box-folder 103: 11)
    - Cold War (Box-folder 104: 1)
    - Common Market (Box-folder 104: 2)
    - Communism (Box-folder 104: 3)
    - Computers (Box-folder 104: 4)
    - Congress (Box-folder 104: 5)
    - Constitutional conventions (Box-folder 104: 6)
    - Copyright (Box-folder 104: 7)
    - Corporate freezeouts (Box-folder 104: 8)
    - Crime (Box-folder 104: 9)
    - Crime (contd.) (Box-folder 105: 1-2)
    - Cuba (Box-folder 105: 3)
    - Culture (Box-folder 105: 4)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - Department of State (Box-folder 105: 6)
    - Draft (Box-folder 105: 7-8)
    - Economy (Box-folder 105: 9)
    - Economy (contd.) (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - Education (Box-folder 106: 2-4)
    - Educational technology (Box-folder 106: 5)
    - Eminent domain (Box-folder 106: 6)
    - Employment (Box-folder 106: 7)
    - Europe (Box-folder 107: 1)
    - Foreign investment and trade (Box-folder 107: 2)
    - Franchise cancellations (Box-folder 107: 3)
    - Germany (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - Great Britain (Box-folder 107: 5)
    - Highway safety (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - India (Box-folder 107: 7)
    - Indonesia (Box-folder 107: 8)
    - Information retrieval (Box-folder 107: 9)
    - Intelligence and national security (Box-folder 107: 10)
    - Interest rates (Box-folder 107: 11)
    - Japan (Box-folder 107: 12)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box-folder 107: 13)
    - Labor (Box-folder 107: 14)
    - Latin America (Box-folder 108: 1)
    - Law schools (Box-folder 108: 2)
    - Legal aid (Box-folder 108: 3)
    - Leisure (Box-folder 108: 4)
    - Local government (Box-folder 108: 5)
    - Long Island Commercial Review (Box-folder 108: 6)
    - Middle East (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - New Left (Box-folder 108: 8)
    - Nuclear arms (Box-folder 108: 9)
    - Oceanography (Box-folder 108: 10)
    - Pate, Maurice (Box-folder 108: 11)
    - Patent licensing (Box-folder 108: 12)
    - Population (Box-folder 108: 13)
    - Poverty (Box-folder 108: 14)
    - Probate (Box-folder 109: 1-2)
    - Products liability (Box-folder 109: 3)
    - Puerto Rico (Box-folder 109: 4)
    - Real estate (Box-folder 109: 5)
    - Real estate (contd.) (Box-folder 110: 1)
    - Refugees (Box-folder 110: 2)
    - Royalties (Box-folder 110: 3)
    - Science and technology (Box-folder 110: 4)
    - Soviet Union (Box-folder 110: 5)
    - Suburban growth (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - Trademark licensing (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - Transportation (Box-folder 110: 8)
    - United Nations (Box-folder 111: 1)
    - Urban renewal and slums (Box-folder 111: 2)
    - Vietnam (Box-folder 111: 3)
    - World hunger (Box-folder 111: 4)
    - World peace through law (Box-folder 111: 5)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 111: 6)
- CASEY FOR CONGRESS COMMITTEE FILE, 1966 (Boxes 111-127)
  Papers of Casey as an unsuccessful candidate for the Republican nomination for Congress in the Third Congressional District of New York.
  - Campaign literature issuances
    - Leaflets (Box-folder 111: 7-9)
    - Leaflets (contd.) (Box-folder 112: 1-2)
    - Stickers and banners (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - Campaign News newsletter (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - Flyers (Box-folder 112: 5)
    - Press releases (Box-folder 112: 6)
    - Leaflet and press release drafts and working materials (Box-folder 112: 7)
    - Newspaper advertisements (Box-folder 113: 1)
    - Radio and television advertisement materials (Box-folder 113: 2)
    - Position papers
      - General (Box-folder 113: 3)
      - Domestic issues (Box-folder 113: 4)
      - Foreign issues (Box-folder 113: 5)
      - Vietnam (Box-folder 113: 6)
    - Position paper drafts and working materials (Box-folder 114: 1)
    - Speech drafts (Box-folder 114: 2)
    - Form letters (Box-folder 114: 3)
    - Republican committeemen form letters (Box-folder 114: 4)
  - Correspondence
    - A-C (Box-folder 114: 5)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - D (Box-folder 114: 7)
    - Davison, F. Trubee (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - Duffy, Eugene H. (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - Dulles, Allen (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - DuPont, Eugene, III (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - E-F (Box-folder 115: 6)
    - Frank, Benjamin (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - G (Box-folder 115: 8)
    - Gillies, Archibald L. (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - Goetz, Sidney M. (Box-folder 115: 10)
    - Guylay, L. Richard (Box-folder 115: 11)
    - H (Box-folder 115: 12)
    - Hall, Leonard W. (Box-folder 115: 13)
    - Hoffmann, Thomas V. (Box-folder 115: 14)
    - I-J (Box-folder 115: 15)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box-folder 115: 16)
    - K (Box-folder 115: 17)
    - Katz, Milton (Box-folder 115: 18)
    - L-M (Box-folder 115: 19)
    - Mazo, Earl (Box-folder 115: 20)
    - N-R (Box-folder 115: 21)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box-folder 115: 22)
    - Romney, George (Box-folder 115: 23)
    - S (Box-folder 116: 1)
    - Safire, William (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - Smith, Owen T. (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - T-Z and unidentified (Box-folder 116: 4)
  - Endorsements
    - General (Box-folder 116: 5)
    - Businessmen for Casey (Box-folder 116: 6)
    - Doctors for Casey (Box-folder 116: 7)
    - Fordham University alumni (Box-folder 116: 8)
    - Hall, Leonard W. (Box-folder 116: 9)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box-folder 116: 10)
    - Keating, Kenneth B. (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - Lawyers for Casey (Box-folder 116: 12)
    - Newspapers (Box-folder 116: 13)
    - Notre Dame University alumni (Box-folder 116: 14)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box-folder 116: 15)
    - St. John's University alumni (Box-folder 116: 16)
    - Scott, Hugh (Box-folder 116: 17)
    - Appointment book (Box-folder 116: 18)
  - Biographical data (Box-folder 117: 1-2)
  - Election certifications (Box-folder 117: 3)
  - Election district handbook for campaign workers (Box-folder 117: 4)
  - Guest registry (blank) (Box-folder 117: 5)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 117: 6)
  - Pollwatchers' handbook (Box-folder 117: 7)
  - Press coverage (Box-folder 117: 8)
  - Press coverage (contd.) (Box-folder 118: 1-4)
  - Public opinion poll data (Box-folder 119: 1)
  - Schedules (Box-folder 119: 2)
  - Lists
    - Administrative (Box-folder 119: 3)
    - Campaign workers (Box-folder 119: 4-5)
    - Club members (Box-folder 119: 6)
    - College alumni (Box-folder 119: 7)
    - Contributors (Box-folder 120: 1)
    - Corporations (Box-folder 120: 2)
    - Democrats (Box-folder 120: 3)
    - Guests at campaign parties (Box-folder 120: 4)
    - Lawyers (Box-folder 120: 5)
    - Newspapers and wire services (Box-folder 120: 6)
    - Officeholders (Box-folder 120: 7)
    - Republican committeemen (Box-folder 120: 8-9)
    - Thank you letters (Box-folder 120: 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 120: 11)
  - Subject file (Box-folder 121)
    Memoranda, correspondence, newsletters, bulletins, and printed matter, mainly re campaign issues and local political personalities
    - Automation (Box-folder 121: 1)
    - Bond, James (Box-folder 121: 2)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 121: 3)
    - Citizens Committee for Peace (Box-folder 121: 4)
    - Civil rights (Box-folder 121: 5)
    - Derounian (Steven B.) campaign (Box-folder 121)
    - Derounian campaign literature (Box-folder 121: 6)
    - Background material re Derounian (Box-folder 121: 7-8)
    - Dirksen, Everett M. (Box-folder 121: 9)
    - Draft (Box-folder 121: 10)
    - Eastern Leukemia Association (Box-folder 121: 11)
    - Education (Box-folder 121: 12)
    - Farm policy (Box-folder 121: 13)
    - Farrington, Palmer D. (Box-folder 121: 14)
    - Federalism (Box-folder 121: 15)
    - Fehrenbach, Edwin J. (Box-folder 121: 16)
    - Foreign policy (Box-folder 122: 1-2)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 122: 3)
    - Government Printing Office (Box-folder 122: 4)
    - Great Society (Box-folder 122: 5)
    - House of Representatives (U.S.) (Box-folder 122: 6)
    - Information industries (Box-folder 123: 1)
    - Labor (Box-folder 123: 2)
    - Latin America (Box-folder 123: 3)
    - Lindsay, John V. (Box-folder 123: 4)
    - Long, Russell B. (Box-folder 123: 5)
    - McNamara, Robert S. (Box-folder 123: 6)
    - Medicare (Box-folder 123: 7)
    - Narcotics (Box-folder 123: 8)
    - Nassau County [New York] Medical Society (Box-folder 123: 9)
    - Nassau County [New York] Republican Committee (Box-folder 123: 10)
    - National security (Box-folder 123: 11)
    - Nickerson, Eugene H. (Box-folder 123: 12)
    - Pearsall, C. Bruce (Box-folder 123: 13)
    - Pollution (Box-folder 123: 14)
    - Poverty (Box-folder 123: 15-16)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 123: 17)
    - Redistricting (Box-folder 123: 18)
    - Republican Party policy (Box-folder 123: 19)
    - Southeast Asia (Box-folder 124: 1)
    - Straus, Nathan (Box-folder 124: 2)
    - Taxation (Box-folder 124: 3-4)
    - Third Congressional District (New York)., Maps and statistics (Box-folder 124: 5)
    - United Nations (Box-folder 124: 6)
    - Urbanization (Box-folder 124: 7)
    - Vietnam
      - General (Box-folder 125: 1-2)
      - Refugees (Box-folder 125: 3)
    - Wolff, Lester L. (Box-folder 125: 4)
    - Wydler, John W. (Box-folder 125: 5)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 125: 6)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 125: 7)
    - Address card files (Box 126)